t3re.com 2016-05-07

# T3 Realty - Privacy Policy

## Privacy Policy 

**(Effective Date: October 1, 2015)**

The website you are accessing (the "Site") is hosted by Constellation Web Solutions, Inc. DBA Market Leader on behalf of one of its real estate industry customers (the "Company"). Market Leader and Company are independent contractors and are not partners or otherwise engaged in any joint venture in delivering the Site. Notwithstanding that fact, this Privacy Policy ("Policy") applies to both Market Leader and Company and as such, any reference to "we", "us" or "our" herein will apply equally to both Market Leader and Company. This Policy explains how personal information is collected, used, and disclosed with respect to your use of the Site, so you can make an informed decision about using the Site.

We reserve the right to change this Policy at any time. If we make any material changes to the Policy, we will post a new statement on the Site and update the effective date set forth above. Therefore, we encourage you to check the effective date of the Policy whenever you visit the Site to see if it has been updated since your last visit.

### INFORMATION WE COLLECT

  * **Personal Information.** As used herein, the term "personal information" means information that specifically identifies an individual (such as a name, address, telephone number, mobile number, or e-mail address,), and information about that individual's location or activities or demographic information when such information is directly linked to personally identifiable information. Personal information does not include "aggregate" information, which is data we collect about the use of the Site or about a group or category of products, services or users, from which individual identities or other personal information has been removed. This Policy in no way restricts or limits our collection and use of aggregate information.
  * **Collection.** Personal information may be collected in a number of ways when you visit the Site. We may collect the personal information that you voluntarily provide to us. For example, when you fill out a form, send us an email, make a request, complete a survey, register for certain services on the Site, or participate in certain activities on the Site, we may ask you to provide personal information such as your e-mail address, name, home or work address or telephone number. We may also collect demographic information, such as your ZIP code, age, gender, and preferences. Information we collect may be combined with information we obtained through other services we offer. We may collect information about your visit to the Site, including the pages you view, the links you click and other actions taken in connection with the Site and services. We may also collect certain standard information that your browser sends to every web site you visit, such as your IP address, browser type and language, access times and referring Web site addresses. If we provide you with various services related to home selling and home buying (e.g., estimates of current market value of homes, moving costs, mortgage or finance costs, current home listings, neighborhood information, etc.), we may collect additional information related to such services.
  * **Cookies and Web Beacons.** We may automatically collect certain information through the use of "cookies" or web beacons. Cookies are small pieces of information or files that are stored on a user's computer by the Web server through a user's browser to enable the site to recognize users who have previously visited them and retain certain information such as customer preferences and history. We may use cookies to identify users, customize their experience on our site or to serve relevant ads. If we combine cookies with or link them to any of the personal information, we would treat this information as personal information. We do not use Web beacons, or similar technology on the Site. However, we may permit third parties to place cookies or Web beacons on the Site to monitor the effectiveness of advertising and for other lawful purposes. A Web beacon, also known as a "Web bug" or a "clear gif" is a small, graphic image on a Web page, Web-based document or in an e-mail message that is designed to allow the site owner or a third party to monitor who is visiting a site and user activity on the site. We do not use (or permit third parties to use) Web beacons to collect personally identifying information about you. If you wish to block, erase, or be warned of cookies, please refer to your browser instructions to learn about these functions. However, if a browser is set to not accept cookies or if a user rejects a cookie, some portions of the Site may not function properly. For example, you may not be able to sign in and may not be able to access certain Site features or services.
  * **Third Party Cookies and Web Beacons; Use of Third Party Ad Networks.** We may also use third parties to serve ads on the Site.These third parties may place cookies, Web beacons or other devices on your computer to collect nonpersonal information, and information provided by these devices may be used, among other things, to deliver advertising targeted to your interests and to better understand the usage and visitation of the Site and the other sites tracked by these third parties. For example, we may allow other companies, called third-party ad servers or ad networks, to display advertisements on the Site. Some of these ad networks may place a persistent cookie on your computer in order to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement. In this way, ad networks may compile information about where you, or others who are using your computer, saw their advertisements and determine which ads are clicked on. This information allows an ad network to deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. We do not have access to the cookies that may be placed by the third-party ad servers or ad networks. This Policy does not apply to, and we are not responsible for, cookies in third party ads, and we encourage you to check the privacy policies of advertisers and/or ad services to learn about their use of cookies and other technology.

### USE OF PERSONAL INFORMATION

We use personal information internally to serve users of the Site, to enhance and extend our relationship with Site users and to facilitate the use of, and administration and operation of, the Site. For example, we may use personal information you provide to deliver services to you, to process your requests or transactions, to provide you with information you request, to personalize content, features and advertising on the Site, to anticipate and resolve problems with the Site, to respond to customer support inquiries, to inform you of other events, promotions, products or services offered by third parties that we think will be of interest to you, to send you relevant survey invitations related to the Site and for our own internal operations, and for any purpose for which such information was collected. We may, from time to time, contact you on behalf of external business partners about a particular offering that may be of interest to you. In those cases, your personal information (e-mail, name, address, telephone number) is not transferred to the third party unless you have consented to such transfer.

### DISCLOSURE OF PERSONAL INFORMATION

Except as set forth in this Policy, we do not disclose, sell, rent, loan, trade or lease any personal information collected on the Site to any third party. We may provide aggregate information to third parties without restriction. We will disclose personal information in the following circumstances: 

  * **Consent.** We may share personal information with third parties when you give us your express or implied consent to do so, such as when you fill out a form requesting certain information from a third party.
  * **Internal Analysis and Operations; Service Providers.** We will use and disclose information about you for our own internal statistical, design or operational purposes, such as to estimate our audience size, measure aggregate traffic patterns, and understand demographic, user interest, purchasing and other trends among our users. We may outsource these tasks and disclose personal information about you to third parties, provided the use and disclosure of your personal information by these third parties is restricted to performance of such tasks. We may also share personal information with other third-party vendors, consultants, and service providers ("Service Providers") who are engaged by or working with us in connection with the operation of the Site or our business In some cases, the Service Provider may be directly collecting the information from you on our behalf. We require our third party vendors to keep such information confidential and to only use the information for the purpose it was provided. However, we are not responsible for the actions of Service Providers or other third parties, nor are we responsible for any additional information you provide directly to these Service Providers or other third parties.
  * **Protection of Company and Others:** We may disclose personal information when we believe it is appropriate to comply with the law (e.g., a lawful subpoena, warrant or court order); to enforce or apply this Policy or our other policies or agreements; to initiate, render, bill, and collect for amounts owed to us; to respond to claims, to protect our or our users' rights, property or safety; or to protect us, our users or the public from fraudulent, abusive, harmful or unlawful activity or use of the Site; or if we reasonably believe that an emergency involving immediate danger of death or serious physical injury to any person requires disclosure of communications or justifies disclosure of records without delay.
  * **Business Transfers.** In addition, information about users of the Site, including personally identifiable information provided by users, may be disclosed or transferred as part of, or during negotiations regarding, any merger, acquisition, debt financing, sale of company assets, as well as in the event of an insolvency, bankruptcy or receivership in which personally identifiable information could be transferred to third parties as one of the business assets of the company.
  * **Co-Branded Services.** Some services available through the Site may be co-branded and offered in conjunction with other companies. If you register for or use such services, then those other companies may also receive any information collected in conjunction with the co-branded services.

### LINKS

Please be aware that we may provide links to third party Web sites from the Site as a service to its users and we are not responsible for the content or information collection practices of those sites. We have no ability to control the privacy and data collection practices of such sites and the privacy policies of such sites may differ from this Policy. Therefore, we encourage you to review and understand the privacy policies of such sites before providing them with any information.

### SECURITY

We use commercially reasonable measures to store and maintain personally identifying information, to protect it from loss, misuse, alternation or destruction by any unauthorized party while it is under our control.

### CHILDREN

We do not intend, and the Site is not designed, to collect personal information from children under the age of 13. If you are under 13 years old, you should not provide information on the Site.

### CHOICE AND ACCESS

You may unsubscribe at any time from receiving non-service related communications from us. Site users have the following options for accessing, changing and deleting personal information previously provided, or opting out of receiving communications from Company or Market Leader: 

  * email us at info@marketleader.com; or
  * call us at the following telephone number: 877-450-0088

### QUESTIONS AND CONCERNS

If you have any questions about this Policy, the practices applicable to the Site, or your dealings with the Site, please contact us at the following address:

Market Leader  
1840 York Road, Timonium MD 21093
